<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>AppOmni Blog (Custom Feed)</title>
  <link>https://appomni.com/article-type/blog/</link>
  <description>Auto-generated every 2 hours</description>
  <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:01:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <item>
    <title>Identity Crisis: Why SaaS Attacks Are Bypassing Your Best Defenses</title>
    <link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2026/02/17/identity-crisis-why-saas-attacks-are-bypassing-your-best-defenses/#new_tab</link>
    <description>To help build a solid foundation for AI adoption, IM firms should source high-quality data, use modern data cloud/hybrid infrastructure, and adopt robust data governance principles. The post Identity Crisis: Why SaaS Attacks Are Bypassing Your Best Defenses appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 01:12:10 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Premium Managed SaaS Security Service | AppOmni Guard</title>
    <link>https://appomni.com/guard-managed-saas-security-service/</link>
    <description>AppOmni Platform Premium Strategic Support Expert-led support for SaaS and AI app security Accelerate your onboarding, implementation, and activation of AppOmni AppOmni’s platform discovers SaaS and AI apps and helps you identify gaps within your security posture that need to be addressed. AppOmni Guard goes a step further by developing your security strategy, guiding your […] The post Premium Managed SaaS Security Service | AppOmni Guard appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:51:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Managed SaaS Threat Hunting | AppOmni Scout</title>
    <link>https://appomni.com/scout-managed-threat-hunting/</link>
    <description>AppOmni Scout – Managed Threat Hunting Service Expertise to find SaaS and AI threats and protect your critical data SaaS and AI threat hunting led by threat experts Security teams don’t have the resources for timely hunting to protect critical data and employees from threats. Monitoring SaaS and AI is complex, time-intensive, and not traditionally […] The post Managed SaaS Threat Hunting | AppOmni Scout appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:48:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>AppOmni at RSAC 2026: Details to Know Before You Go</title>
    <link>https://appomni.com/blog/appomni-rsa-conference-2026/</link>
    <description>AppOmni shares RSA Conference 2026 insights to improve SaaS and AI security. The post AppOmni at RSAC 2026: Details to Know Before You Go appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 19:56:27 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Request Strategy Session at RSA 2026</title>
    <link>https://appomni.com/lp/rsa-2026-request-strategy-session/</link>
    <description>Request a SaaS &amp; AI Security Strategy Session at RSA 2026 How exposed are your most critical SaaS platforms right now? Apps like Salesforce, ServiceNow, Microsoft 365, and Google Workspace sit at the center of enterprise operations and increasingly they’re where SaaS and AI risk concentrates. Meet privately with AppOmni threat researchers during RSAC for […] The post Request Strategy Session at RSA 2026 appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 19:37:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence security vulnerability uncovered</title>
    <link>https://www.news5cleveland.com/about-us/as-seen-on/morning-digest-leaders-preparing-for-possible-ice-agents-in-ohio-this-week#new_tab</link>
    <description>Aaron Costello with AppOmni tells Good Morning Cleveland anchor Mike Brookbank more about the flaw in the ServiceNow platform. The post Artificial Intelligence security vulnerability uncovered appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:14:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Panera Bread breach: ShinyHunters claims hack of 14 million customers’ data</title>
    <link>https://mashable.com/article/panera-bread-breach-shinyhunters-voice-phishing-14-million-customers#new_tab</link>
    <description>“This aligns closely with Okta’s recent warnings about vishing-driven SSO compromise targeting Okta, Microsoft, and Google." — Cory Michal, AppOmni. The post Panera Bread breach: ShinyHunters claims hack of 14 million customers’ data appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:10:35 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Book a Security Strategy Session with AppOmni</title>
    <link>https://appomni.com/lp/book-a-meeting/</link>
    <description>How exposed are your most critical SaaS platforms? Apps like Salesforce, ServiceNow, Microsoft 365, and Google Workspace sit at the center of enterprise operations and increasingly they’re where SaaS and AI risk concentrates. Book a meeting with the AppOmni team, and get a focused SaaS and AI Security Strategy Session to make high-impact decisions across […] The post Book a Security Strategy Session with AppOmni appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:10:19 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>10 ways AI can inflict unprecedented damage in 2026</title>
    <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/10-ways-ai-will-do-unprecedented-damage-in-2026-experts-warn/#new_tab</link>
    <description>"By trying to make AI as powerful as it can be, organizations may misconfigure settings, leading to overpermissions and data exposure." — Melissa Ruzzi, AppOmni. The post 10 ways AI can inflict unprecedented damage in 2026 appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:29:08 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Agentic AI Security in ServiceNow: Experts Explain Key Concepts You Need to Know</title>
    <link>https://nowben.com/agentic-ai-security-in-servicenow-experts-explain-key-concepts-you-need-to-know/#new_tab</link>
    <description>It's important to ensure agentic AI logs are being centralized in the same place as other security alerts. The post Agentic AI Security in ServiceNow: Experts Explain Key Concepts You Need to Know appeared first on AppOmni .</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:32:45 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
