&lt;?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?&gt;
&lt;rss version="2.0"&gt;
&lt;channel&gt;
  &lt;title&gt;Cyjax Resources (Blog filter) (Custom Feed)&lt;/title&gt;
  &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources?0402ca75_category_equal=Blog&lt;/link&gt;
  &lt;description&gt;Auto-generated periodically&lt;/description&gt;
  &lt;lastBuildDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:06 GMT&lt;/lastBuildDate&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;OCRFix: Botnet Trojan delivered through ClickFix and EtherHiding  - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/ocrfix-botnet-trojan-delivered-through-clickfix-and-etherhiding&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;During routine analysis, CYJAX identified a typosquatting phishing campaign which impersonated the Optical Character Recognition (OCR) tool Tesseract OCR. What originally appeared to be a ClickFix attack evolved into a sophisticated campaign delivering multi-stage malware deployments. The campaign, which CYJAX has titled OCRFix, made use of heavy obfuscation and defence evasion techniques, including EtherHiding. &lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:00 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;CYJAX in 2025: A Year in Retrospect  - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/cyjax-in-2025-a-year-in-retrospect&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;2025 was a defining year for CYJAX. With a bold rebrand, product innovation, and growing industry recognition, we strengthened our mission to empower organisations with analyst-enriched threat intelligence. This blog takes a retrospective look at CYJAX in 2025, a year that shaped our growth and direction.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:00 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Russian hacktivist attacks against the UK - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/russian-hacktivist-attacks-against-the-uk&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;This blog analyses #OpUK 2026, examining how pro-Russian hacktivist groups targeted UK government, financial, and transport organisations in response to geopolitical support for Ukraine.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:01 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;AI Is Fast – But Humans Are Smarter: Why Analyst Insight Still Wins in Cybersecurity  - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/ai-is-fast-but-humans-are-smarter-why-analyst-insight-still-wins-in-cybersecurity&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;AI accelerates detection, but human analysts deliver context, judgement and strategic insight. In modern cybersecurity, the real advantage lies in combining both.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:01 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;CYJAX vs. SOC Radar: Different Approaches to Cyber Threat Intelligence  - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/cyjax-vs-soc-radar-different-approaches-to-cyber-threat-intelligence&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;A detailed comparison of CYJAX and SOC Radar, exploring differences in automation, analyst-led investigations, RFIs, and intelligence depth to help security teams choose the right CTI platform.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:01 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Cyber Threat Intelligence Trends Financial Institutions Can’t Ignore in 2026 - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/cyber-threat-intelligence-trends-financial-institutions-cant-ignore-in-2026&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;Financial institutions face growing cyber risk as AI-driven attacks, cloud complexity, and regulatory pressure reshape the threat landscape. This blog explores the cyber threat intelligence trends shaping financial services in 2026 and what organisations need to prepare for.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:02 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Dark Web Marketplaces 2026: Emerging Cybercrime Trends and Threats for CISOs - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/dark-web-marketplaces-2026-emerging-cybercrime-trends-and-threats-for-cisos&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;Dark web marketplaces continue to fuel cybercrime in 2026. This blog explores emerging trends, what threat actors are trading, and why dark web monitoring is essential for organisations.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:02 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Inside the Surge of Cyber Attacks Targeting Manufacturing  - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/inside-the-surge-of-cyber-attacks-targeting-manufacturing&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;Manufacturing is facing a sharp rise in cyber attacks, driven by increased connectivity, IT/OT convergence, and complex supply chains. This blog explores the key threats targeting the sector and explains why proactive, intelligence-led cybersecurity is essential to protect operations and reduce risk.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:02 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Top Cybersecurity Events to Attend in London in 2026 - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/top-cybersecurity-events-to-attend-in-london-in-2026&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;From global summits to exclusive CISO gatherings, these top cybersecurity events in London for 2026 offer valuable insights, networking opportunities, and expert-led discussions to help professionals stay ahead of emerging cyber threats.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:03 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;How Threat Intelligence Is Reshaping the CISO Agenda in 2026  - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/how-threat-intelligence-is-reshaping-the-ciso-agenda-in-2026&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;A practical look at how CISOs can turn the lessons of 2025 into actionable threat intelligence strategies for 2026.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:03 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Threat Intelligence Platforms: From Data to Actionable Insight - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/threat-intelligence-platforms-from-data-to-actionable-insight&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;Learn how a Threat Intelligence Platform (TIP) centralises, enriches, and prioritises threat data to deliver actionable cyber intelligence at scale.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:03 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Beyond the Threats: The People of CYJAX - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/beyond-the-threats-the-people-of-cyjax-5&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;Beyond the Threats: The People of CYJAX - CYJAX&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:03 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Top 25 Cybersecurity Breaches in the UK: What Went Wrong  - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/blog/top-25-cybersecurity-breaches-in-the-uk-what-went-wrong&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;A deep dive into the UK’s most significant cybersecurity breaches, examining how they happened, what went wrong, and the lessons organisations can learn. From household brands to public institutions, these incidents reveal the real cost of poor cyber resilience.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:04 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;The Impact of The Cybercriminal Landscape Against Manufacturing - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/white-paper/the-impact-of-the-cybercriminal-landscape-against-manufacturing&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;November 2025, including the rise of advanced social engineering, targeted phishing campaigns, ransomware operations, and the growing role of initial access brokers. Using real-world incidents and threat intelligence data, it highlights how attackers gain access, the scale of financial impact, and why manufacturing remains a high-value target.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:04 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;The Impact of the Cybercriminal Landscape Against Finance - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/white-paper/the-impact-of-the-cybercriminal-landscape-against-finance&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;The financial sector remains one of the most attractive targets for cybercriminals due to the value of the data it holds and the critical role it plays in global economic stability. Between late 2024 and November 2025, threat actors increasingly leveraged social engineering, ransomware, and third-party compromise to exploit financial organisations, often resulting in significant financial, operational, and reputational impact. This whitepaper examines how these evolving tactics have shaped the cyber threat landscape for the finance sector over this period.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:04 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Compromise against the NHS - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/white-paper/compromise-against-the-nhs&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;This whitepaper explores the growing cyber threats targeting the NHS, revealing how attackers exploit outdated systems and human error to gain financial and data advantages. Learn how these compromises strain critical healthcare resources and what can be done to mitigate them.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:04 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Visa And Immigration Fraud Affecting The UK - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/white-paper/visa-and-immigration-fraud-affecting-the-uk&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;Explore how scammers exploit the UK visa system through fake jobs, phishing, and organised crime in CYJAX's visa and immigration fraud report.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:05 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;The ROI of Cyber Threat Intelligence:  A Framework for CISOs - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/white-paper/the-roi-of-cyber-threat-intelligence-a-framework-for-cisos&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;This whitepaper explores how CISOs can measure and maximise the ROI of cyber threat intelligence, turning intelligence insights into tangible business value and strategic advantage.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:05 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;How Threat Actors Exploit AI Tools: A CTI Perspective - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/white-paper/how-threat-actors-exploit-ai-tools-a-cti-perspective&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;In this whitepaper, CYJAX explores how threat actors are weaponising AI, backed by real-world intelligence and actionable insights.&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:06 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
    &lt;title&gt;Hackers Hate This: The New Playbook for Retail Threat Defence - CYJAX&lt;/title&gt;
    &lt;link&gt;https://www.cyjax.com/resources/white-paper/retail-security-reinvented-leveraging-threat-intelligence-to-stay-ahead&lt;/link&gt;
    &lt;description&gt;Hackers Hate This: The New Playbook for Retail Threat Defence - CYJAX&lt;/description&gt;
    &lt;pubDate&gt;Thu, 26 Feb 2026 02:53:06 GMT&lt;/pubDate&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/channel&gt;
&lt;/rss&gt;
