<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Deception.Pro Blog (Custom Feed)</title>
  <link>https://blog.deception.pro/</link>
  <description>Auto-generated every 2 hours</description>
  <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:03:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <item>
    <title>[Op Report] Hands-on-Keyboard Intrusion Abusing Multiple RMMs</title>
    <link>https://blog.deception.pro/blog/hok-intrusion-abusing-multiple-rmms-jan2026</link>
    <description>Proofpoint observed a hands-on-keyboard intrusion where an operator abused 
multiple RMM platforms—including Bluetrait, Fleetdeck, Level, and MSP360
—after initial access via a malicious PDF “missing Adobe plugin” lure. The 
activity underscores a growing reality: attackers are increasingly using 
legitimate IT tooling as a resilient intrusion framework.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>[Update] Deception.Pro Jan 2026</title>
    <link>https://blog.deception.pro/blog/deceptionpro-platform-update-jan-2026</link>
    <description>The January 2026 Deception.Pro update introduces industry based replica 
browsing for Premium users, expanded and more reliable malware auto 
detonation across common delivery formats, improved artifact handling with 
VirusTotal linking, and broad stability enhancements, while laying the 
groundwork for dedicated KVM infrastructure, TLS inspection, and memory 
dump support.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:07:19 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>[Op Report] CastleRAT Campaign leads to Hands-on-Keyboard ATO Operations</title>
    <link>https://blog.deception.pro/blog/castlerat-dec2025-hok-ato</link>
    <description>This Deception.Pro operation captured a multi-stage malware intrusion 
culminating in hands-on-keyboard (HoK) activity focused exclusively on 
account takeover (ATO): not ransomware staging or enterprise lateral 
movement.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:23:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>[Op Report] Oyster → Vidar → Supper socks shell Campaign Leads to Hands-on-Keyboard Activity</title>
    <link>https://blog.deception.pro/blog/oyster-vidar-hok-dec2025</link>
    <description>A recent Deception.Pro operation involving a replica victim in the travel 
and tourism sector revealed a multi-stage infection beginning with an 
Oyster malware dropper masquerading as a Microsoft Teams installer.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>[Update] New Features Added!</title>
    <link>https://blog.deception.pro/blog/updated-nov4-2025</link>
    <description>A list of recent updates and features.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:23:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
